BRYAN VIRIYA KURNIAWAN

Purwakarta, Indonesia • +62-838-2062-2645 • viriyabryan@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Bryan (18) is an experienced programmer, designer and marketer with demonstrated history of working in higher education and company. He is passionate, creative, initiative and eagerness to self learn to develop latest soft and hard skill.

CORE COMPETENCIES

•	Dragramm	ına
•	Programm	11111

Design Thinking

Web Development

Graphic Design

Complex Problem Solving

Adobe

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

BSc in Computer Science | Bina Nusantara University

2021 - Present

Cummulative GPA: 3,74

High School Diploma in Science | SMAN 1 Purwakarta

2018-2021

- Top 2 Class Ranking For 3 Years
- One Of The Selected Finalists SNMPTN

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marketing | Binus University - Part-time

2021 - Present

Binus is a one of the best private university in Indonesia

- Carry out promotion and marketing of Binus University to prospective students
- Promoted Binus to 100+ prospective students

Videographer & Video editor | Binus University - Part-time

2021 - Present

Binus is a one of the best private university in Indonesia

- Shot and edited Binus's promotional videos
- Made 10+ binus's promotional videos

Swimming Coach | Yordan Swimming Club - *Part-time*

2020 - 2021

Yordan Swimming Club is a swimming club in Purwakarta, Indonesia

- · Training and teaching swimmers athlete
- Helped 15+ swimmer athletes reach the target

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Head of PMV Budi Dharma

2021 - 2022

PMV Budi Dharma is a Buddhist youth organization in Purwakarta, Indonesia

- · Leading and controlling all religious activities of Buddhist children and youth
- Taught and Helped 20+ Buddhist children to understand Buddhism

Committe of Keluarga Mahasiswa Buddhis Dhammavaddhana BINUS

KMBD BINUS is a Buddhist organization in Binus Univesity

- · Coordinating and controlling all organizations event, and social activities
- Shared and taught all about Buddhism to 20+ students

Head of SMAN 1 Swimming Extracurricular

2020 - 2021

SMAN 1 Swimming Extracurricular is a sport organization in SMAN 1 Purwakarta, Indonesia

- · Leading, coordinating and controlling all extracurricular activities
- Taught and Helped 30+ beginner swimmer to swim well

AWARDS, AND CERTIFICATIONS

- 2nd place in National Competition "Cepat Tepat Dhamma" (Sekber PMVBI, 2019)
- Complete C Course Programming (Sololearn, 2022)
- SoCS International Seminar: "Multimodal Machine Speech Chain" (Binus University, 2021)

2021 - 2022